Center for Environmental Management Records UA096
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Courses and workshops, 1985 -- 1995; 1987 -- 1994; UA096.002; 8.4 Linear Feet
  This series is arranged chronologically. General descriptive course information at the beginning of series. There are course booklets and other general information regarding the annual review courses are placed at the end of all the courses but prior to the workshops. Workshops arranged separately and chronologically after courses.
  - P&P Annual Review + Asbestos Abatement Pamphlet, UA096.002.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - May 20, 1985; UA096.002.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - June 20, 1985 Agendas, UA096.002.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - June 21, 1985; UA096.002.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - Sept 30, 1985; UA096.002.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Oct. 16, 1985; UA096.002.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Nov 14, 1985; UA096.002.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Dec. 17, 1985; UA096.002.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Jan 13-17, 1986; UA096.002.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Participants List, Asbestos in Buildings Seminar, 11, March 1986, UA096.002.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence: Glovebag Removal Workshop 3/12/86, 1986; UA096.002.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - March 17-21, 1986; UA096.002.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - May 20-22, 1986; UA096.002.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - June 20, 1986; UA096.002.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - August 11, 1986; UA096.002.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Sept. 8-12, 1986; UA096.002.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - October 8, 1986; UA096.002.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - Dec 2, 1986; UA096.002.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - Participant List/ Certificates December 9-11, 1986; UA096.002.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - October 29, 1987; UA096.002.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - Jan 26-30, 1987; UA096.002.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - Correspondence February 24-25, 1987; UA096.002.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - March 18, 1987; UA096.002.006.00023 (Box 6)
  - April 6-10, 1987; UA096.002.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - May 20, 1987; UA096.002.006.00025 (Box 6)
  - June 22-26, 1987; UA096.002.006.00026 (Box 6)
  - Caligraphy, 1987; UA096.002.006.00027 (Box 6)
  - Agenda, 1987; UA096.002.006.00028 (Box 6)
  - Brochure, 1987; UA096.002.006.00029 (Box 6)
  - Course Faculty, UA096.002.006.00030 (Box 6)
  - Registrations, 1987; UA096.002.006.00031 (Box 6)
  - Accomodations- Quality Inn Contract, 1987; UA096.002.006.00032 (Box 6)
  - Exam Results, 1987; UA096.002.006.00033 (Box 6)
  - Breakdown of Sessions, UA096.002.006.00034 (Box 6)
  - Confirmation Packets, 1987; UA096.002.006.00035 (Box 6)
  - Exam, 1987; UA096.002.006.00036 (Box 6)
  - Grade Letters, 1987; UA096.002.006.00037 (Box 6)
  - Evaluations, UA096.002.006.00038 (Box 6)
  - Course Evaluations, 1987; UA096.002.006.00039 (Box 6)
  - Speaker Correspondence, UA096.002.006.00040 (Box 6)
  - July 27-31, 1987; UA096.002.006.00041 (Box 6)
  - August 10-14, 1987; UA096.002.006.00042 (Box 6)
  - Sept. 16, 1987; UA096.002.006.00043 (Box 6)
  - August 17-21, 1987; UA096.002.006.00044 (Box 6)
  - Oct. 19-23, 1987; UA096.002.006.00045 (Box 6)
  - Nov 2-6, 1987; UA096.002.006.00046 (Box 6)
  - Nov 16-20, 1987; UA096.002.006.00047 (Box 6)
  - Nov 30- Dec 4, 1987; UA096.002.006.00048 (Box 6)
  - Jan 4-8, 1988; UA096.002.006.00049 (Box 6)
  - Course Participants Registration, 1988; UA096.002.006.00050 (Box 6)
  - Agenda, 1988; UA096.002.006.00051 (Box 6)
  - Agenda, UA096.002.006.00052 (Box 6)
  - Course Faculty/ Speakers, 1988; UA096.002.006.00053 (Box 6)
  - Examination, 1988; UA096.002.006.00054 (Box 6)
  - Exam and Quiz Scores, 1988; UA096.002.006.00055 (Box 6)
  - Speaker Confirmation Packets, 1987; UA096.002.006.00056 (Box 6)
  - Participant Confirmation Packet, 1987; UA096.002.006.00057 (Box 6)
  - Evaluation Results, 1988; UA096.002.006.00058 (Box 6)
  - Daily Attendance & Exam Sign-Out, 1988; UA096.002.006.00059 (Box 6)
  - Calligraphy List January 11-13, 1988; UA096.002.006.00060 (Box 6)
  - Calligraphy List January 14-15, 1988; UA096.002.006.00061 (Box 6)
  - U.S. Dept. of Labor List, 1988; UA096.002.006.00062 (Box 6)
  - Grade Letters, 1988; UA096.002.006.00063 (Box 6)
  - Business Cards Xerox, 1988; UA096.002.006.00064 (Box 6)
  - Accomodations, 1987; UA096.002.006.00065 (Box 6)
  - Jan 25-29, 1988; UA096.002.006.00066 (Box 6)
  - Feb 11, 1988; UA096.002.006.00067 (Box 6)
  - Feb 15-19, 1988; UA096.002.006.00068 (Box 6)
  - Feb 25, 1988; UA096.002.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - Feb 29 - Mar 4 1988, UA096.002.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - March 21-25, 1988; UA096.002.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - March 28 - April 1, 1988; UA096.002.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - March 30-31, 1988; UA096.002.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - April 11-15, 1988; UA096.002.007.00006 (Box 7)
  - April 18-22, 1988; UA096.002.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - April 20, 1988; UA096.002.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - April 25-29, 1988; UA096.002.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - May 3, 1988; UA096.002.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - May 16-20, 1988; UA096.002.007.00011 (Box 7)
  - May 23-27, 1988; UA096.002.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - May 25-26, 1988; UA096.002.007.00013 (Box 7)
  - June 6-10, 1988; UA096.002.007.00014 (Box 7)
  - June 13-17, 1988; UA096.002.007.00015 (Box 7)
  - June 20-24, 1988; UA096.002.007.00016 (Box 7)
  - June 27-30, 1988; UA096.002.007.00017 (Box 7)
  - June 27, July 1, 1988; UA096.002.007.00018 (Box 7)
  - July 11, 1988; UA096.002.007.00019 (Box 7)
  - July 11-15, 1988; UA096.002.007.00020 (Box 7)
  - July 18-22, 1988; UA096.002.007.00021 (Box 7)
  - July 19, 1988; UA096.002.007.00022 (Box 7)
  - July 20-21, 1988; UA096.002.007.00023 (Box 7)
  - August 1-5, 1988; UA096.002.007.00024 (Box 7)
  - August 8-12, 1988; UA096.002.007.00025 (Box 7)
  - August 15-19, 1988; UA096.002.007.00026 (Box 7)
  - Sept. 1, 1988; UA096.002.007.00027 (Box 7)
  - New York- Retake Exam September 9. 1988, UA096.002.007.00028 (Box 7)
  - Sept. 12-16, 1988; UA096.002.008.00001 (Box 8)
  - Sept. 28-29, 1988; UA096.002.008.00002 (Box 8)
  - Oct. 3-7, 1988; UA096.002.008.00003 (Box 8)
  - October 17-21, 1988; UA096.002.008.00004 (Box 8)
  - Oct. 19-20, 1988; UA096.002.008.00005 (Box 8)
  - Nov 14, 1988; UA096.002.008.00006 (Box 8)
  - Carpenters Training Course October 24-28, 1988; UA096.002.008.00007 (Box 8)
  - Nov 16-17, 1988; UA096.002.008.00008 (Box 8)
  - Nov 28- Dec 2, 1988; UA096.002.008.00009 (Box 8)
  - Dec. 1, 1988; UA096.002.008.00010 (Box 8)
  - Dec. 5-9, 1988; UA096.002.008.00011 (Box 8)
  - Dec. 5-9, 1988; UA096.002.008.00012 (Box 8)
  - Jan 5, 1989; UA096.002.008.00013 (Box 8)
  - Jan 9-13, 1989; UA096.002.008.00014 (Box 8)
  - Jan 11-12, 1989; UA096.002.008.00015 (Box 8)
  - Jan 18, 1989; UA096.002.008.00016 (Box 8)
  - Jan 23-27, 1989; UA096.002.008.00017 (Box 8)
  - Feb 6-10, 1989; UA096.002.008.00018 (Box 8)
  - Feb 13-17, 1989; UA096.002.008.00019 (Box 8)
  - Feb 23 1989, UA096.002.008.00020 (Box 8)
  - Feb 27- March 1, 1989; UA096.002.008.00021 (Box 8)
  - March 7-8, 1989; UA096.002.008.00022 (Box 8)
  - March 13-17, 1989; UA096.002.008.00023 (Box 8)
  - March 16, 1989; UA096.002.008.00024 (Box 8)
  - Mar 20-24, 1989; UA096.002.008.00025 (Box 8)
  - March 22-23, 1989; UA096.002.008.00026 (Box 8)
  - April 3-4, 1989; UA096.002.008.00027 (Box 8)
  - April 3-7, 1989; UA096.002.008.00028 (Box 8)
  - April 10-14, 1989; UA096.002.008.00029 (Box 8)
  - May 10-11, 1989; UA096.002.008.00030 (Box 8)
  - May 15-19, 1989; UA096.002.008.00031 (Box 8)
  - May 23, 1989; UA096.002.008.00032 (Box 8)
  - 1989 June 19-23, UA096.002.008.00033 (Box 8)
  - Agenda June 26-30, 1989; UA096.002.008.00034 (Box 8)
  - 1989 July 10-13, UA096.002.008.00035 (Box 8)
  - July 17-18, 1989; UA096.002.008.00036 (Box 8)
  - July 19, 1989; UA096.002.008.00037 (Box 8)
  - Jul. 31 - Aug. 4, 1989; UA096.002.008.00038 (Box 8)
  - Aug 14-18, 1989; UA096.002.008.00039 (Box 8)
  - Aug 16-17, 1989; UA096.002.008.00040 (Box 8)
  - Sept 7, 1989; UA096.002.008.00041 (Box 8)
  - Sept 8, 1989; UA096.002.008.00042 (Box 8)
  - Sept 11-15, 1989; UA096.002.008.00043 (Box 8)
  - Sept. 12-14, 1989; UA096.002.008.00044 (Box 8)
  - Oct 2-6, 1989; UA096.002.008.00045 (Box 8)
  - Oct 12, 1989; UA096.002.008.00046 (Box 8)
  - Oct 13, 1989; UA096.002.008.00047 (Box 8)
  - Oct 16-20, 1989; UA096.002.008.00048 (Box 8)
  - Contractor Grade Letter, 1989; UA096.002.008.00049 (Box 8)
  - Agenda, 1989; UA096.002.008.00050 (Box 8)
  - Course Faculty/ Speakers, 1989; UA096.002.008.00051 (Box 8)
  - Course Participants/ Regist., 1989; UA096.002.008.00052 (Box 8)
  - Daily attend. exam sign-out, 1989; UA096.002.009.00001 (Box 9)
  - Speaker confirmation packets, 1989; UA096.002.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Examination results, 1989; UA096.002.009.00003 (Box 9)
  - Grade letters-workers, 1989; UA096.002.009.00004 (Box 9)
  - Grade letters-supervisor, 1989; UA096.002.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Department of labor list, 1989; UA096.002.009.00006 (Box 9)
  - Evaluation results, 1989; UA096.002.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - Missing chapter, 1989; UA096.002.009.00008 (Box 9)
  - Nov 20, 1989; UA096.002.009.00009 (Box 9)
  - Nov 27 - Dec 1, 1989; UA096.002.009.00010 (Box 9)
  - Dec 4-8, 1989; UA096.002.009.00011 (Box 9)
  - Dec 27 - 28, 1989; UA096.002.009.00012 (Box 9)
  - Jan 4 - 12, 1990; UA096.002.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - Jan 16 - 19, 1990; UA096.002.009.00014 (Box 9)
  - Jan 18, 1990; UA096.002.009.00015 (Box 9)
  - Jan 22 - 26, 1990; UA096.002.009.00016 (Box 9)
  - Jan 23, 1990; UA096.002.009.00017 (Box 9)
  - Jan 29 - Feb 2, 1990; UA096.002.009.00018 (Box 9)
  - Feb 5 - 9, 1990; UA096.002.009.00019 (Box 9)
  - Feb 12 - 16, 1990; UA096.002.009.00020 (Box 9)
  - Feb 13, 1990; UA096.002.009.00021 (Box 9)
  - Feb 20-23, 1990; UA096.002.009.00022 (Box 9)
  - Feb 26 - Mar 2, 1990; UA096.002.009.00023 (Box 9)
  - March 5 - 9, 1990; UA096.002.009.00024 (Box 9)
  - March 12 - 16, 1990; UA096.002.009.00025 (Box 9)
  - March 13, 1990; UA096.002.009.00026 (Box 9)
  - March 26 - 30, 1990; UA096.002.009.00027 (Box 9)
  - April 2 - 6, 1990; UA096.002.009.00028 (Box 9)
  - April 5 - 6, 9 - 11, 1990; UA096.002.009.00029 (Box 9)
  - April 9 - 13, 1990; UA096.002.009.00030 (Box 9)
  - April 17 - 18, 1990; UA096.002.009.00031 (Box 9)
  - April 18 - 19, 1990; UA096.002.009.00032 (Box 9)
  - April 23 - 26, 1990; UA096.002.009.00033 (Box 9)
  - April 24, 1990; UA096.002.009.00034 (Box 9)
  - April 30 - May 4, 1990; UA096.002.009.00035 (Box 9)
  - May 7 - 11, 1990; UA096.002.009.00036 (Box 9)
  - May 15, 1990; UA096.002.009.00037 (Box 9)
  - May 30 - 31, 1990; UA096.002.009.00038 (Box 9)
  - June 12, 1990; UA096.002.009.00039 (Box 9)
  - June 13 - 15, 1990; UA096.002.009.00040 (Box 9)
  - June 18 - 22, 1990; UA096.002.009.00041 (Box 9)
  - General physics - 40-hr Haswoper June 25 - 29, 1990; UA096.002.009.00042 (Box 9)
  - July 6, 1990; UA096.002.009.00043 (Box 9)
  - July 9 - 13, 1990; UA096.002.009.00044 (Box 9)
  - July 16 - 19, 1990; UA096.002.009.00045 (Box 9)
  - Aug 2, 1990; UA096.002.009.00046 (Box Shared 80)
  - Aug 13 - 15, 1990; UA096.002.009.00047 (Box 9)
  - August 14 - 15, 1990; UA096.002.009.00048 (Box 9)
  - Aug 16, 1990; UA096.002.009.00049 (Box 9)
  - Aug 20 - 24, 1990; UA096.002.009.00050 (Box 9)
  - Sept 4 - 7, 1990; UA096.002.009.00051 (Box 9)
  - Sept 10 - 14, 1990; UA096.002.009.00052 (Box 9)
  - Sept 20, 1990; UA096.002.009.00053 (Box 9)
  - Sept 24 - 28, 1990; UA096.002.009.00054 (Box 9)
  - Sept 24 - 28, 1990; UA096.002.009.00055 (Box 9)
  - Oct 1 - 3, 1990; UA096.002.009.00056 (Box 9)
  - Oct 1 - 5, 1990; UA096.002.009.00057 (Box 9)
  - Oct 5, 1990; UA096.002.009.00058 (Box 9)
  - Oct 9 - 12, 1990; UA096.002.009.00059 (Box 9)
  - Oct. 15 - 19, 1990; UA096.002.009.00060 (Box 9)
  - Oct 23 - 24, 1990; UA096.002.009.00061 (Box 9)
  - Oct 25, 1990; UA096.002.009.00062 (Box 9)
  - Oct 29 - Noc, 1990; UA096.002.009.00063 (Box 9)
  - Nov 13 - 16, 1990; UA096.002.009.00064 (Box 9)
  - Nov 26 - 28, 1990; UA096.002.009.00065 (Box 9)
  - Nov 29, 1990; UA096.002.009.00066 (Box 9)
  - Agenda Dec 4, 1990; UA096.002.009.00067 (Box 9)
  - Dec 10 - 14, 1990; UA096.002.009.00068 (Box 9)
  - Dec 12, 1990; UA096.002.010.00001 (Box 8)
  - Dec 27-28, 1990; UA096.002.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - Feb 4-7, 1991; UA096.002.010.00003 (Box 10)
  - Jan 7-9, 1991; UA096.002.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - Jan 17, 1991; UA096.002.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - Jan 22-25, 1991; UA096.002.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - Jan 28 - Feb 1, 1991; UA096.002.010.00007 (Box 10)
  - Feb 11-13, 1991; UA096.002.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - Feb 14, 1991; UA096.002.010.00009 (Box 10)
  - Feb 15, 1991; UA096.002.010.00010 (Box 10)
  - Feb 25-18, 1991; UA096.002.010.00011 (Box 10)
  - Feb 27, 1991; UA096.002.010.00012 (Box 10)
  - March 1, 1991; UA096.002.010.00013 (Box 10)
  - March 13, 1991; UA096.002.010.00014 (Box 10)
  - March 18, 1991; UA096.002.010.00015 (Box 10)
  - March 19, 1991; UA096.002.010.00016 (Box 10)
  - March 25-29, 1991; UA096.002.010.00017 (Box 10)
  - March 28, 1991; UA096.002.010.00018 (Box 10)
  - April 1-4, 1991; UA096.002.010.00019 (Box 10)
  - April 17, 1991; UA096.002.010.00020 (Box 10)
  - April 18, 1991; UA096.002.010.00021 (Box 10)
  - April 22-24, 1991; UA096.002.010.00022 (Box 10)
  - May 14-17, 1991; UA096.002.010.00023 (Box 10)
  - May 28-30, 1991; UA096.002.010.00024 (Box 10)
  - May 29, 1991; UA096.002.010.00025 (Box 10)
  - July 15-19, 1991; UA096.002.010.00026 (Box 10)
  - June 19, 1991; UA096.002.010.00027 (Box 10)
  - July 29, 1991; UA096.002.010.00028 (Box 10)
  - July 30, 1991; UA096.002.010.00029 (Box 10)
  - Aug 7-9, 1991; UA096.002.010.00030 (Box 10)
  - August 12-15, 1991; UA096.002.010.00031 (Box 10)
  - Sept 5, 1991; UA096.002.010.00032 (Box 10)
  - Sept 18-20, 1991; UA096.002.010.00033 (Box 10)
  - Sept. 24, 1991; UA096.002.010.00034 (Box 10)
  - Sept 30 - Oct 4, 1991; UA096.002.010.00035 (Box 10)
  - October 10, 1991; UA096.002.010.00036 (Box 10)
  - October 15-18, 1991; UA096.002.010.00037 (Box 10)
  - October 28 - Nov 1, 1991; UA096.002.010.00038 (Box 10)
  - October 31, 1991; UA096.002.010.00039 (Box 10)
  - Nov 12, 1991; UA096.002.010.00040 (Box 10)
  - Nov 13, 1991; UA096.002.010.00041 (Box 10)
  - Dec 6, 1991; UA096.002.010.00042 (Box 10)
  - Jan 9, 1991; UA096.002.010.00043 (Box 10)
  - Jan 10, 1992; UA096.002.010.00044 (Box 10)
  - Jan 13-17, 1992; UA096.002.010.00045 (Box 10)
  - Feb 3-5, 1992; UA096.002.010.00046 (Box 10)
  - Feb 20, 1992; UA096.002.010.00047 (Box 10)
  - Feb 21, 1992; UA096.002.010.00048 (Box 10)
  - Feb 28, 1992; UA096.002.010.00049 (Box 10)
  - March 2-6, 1991; UA096.002.010.00050 (Box 10)
  - March 18-20, 1992; UA096.002.010.00051 (Box 10)
  - March 23-36, 1992; UA096.002.010.00052 (Box 10)
  - March 26, 1992; UA096.002.010.00053 (Box 10)
  - March 27, 1992; UA096.002.010.00054 (Box 10)
  - March 30, 1992; UA096.002.010.00055 (Box 10)
  - March 31, 1992; UA096.002.010.00056 (Box 10)
  - April 6-10, 1992; UA096.002.010.00057 (Box 10)
  - May 7, 1992; UA096.002.010.00058 (Box 10)
  - May 8, 1992; UA096.002.010.00059 (Box 10)
  - May 11-15, 1992; UA096.002.010.00060 (Box 10)
  - June 29, 1992; UA096.002.010.00061 (Box 10)
  - June 30, 1992; UA096.002.010.00062 (Box 10)
  - July 27, 1992; UA096.002.010.00063 (Box 10)
  - Aug 24-28, 1992; UA096.002.010.00064 (Box 10)
  - Aug 31, 1992; UA096.002.010.00065 (Box 10)
  - Sept. 1, 1992; UA096.002.010.00066 (Box 10)
  - Sept. 22-25, 1992; UA096.002.010.00067 (Box 10)
  - Sept. 28-30, 1992; UA096.002.010.00068 (Box 10)
  - Oct 21, 1992; UA096.002.010.00069 (Box 10)
  - Oct 29, 1992; UA096.002.010.00070 (Box 10)
  - Oct 30, 1992; UA096.002.010.00071 (Box 10)
  - Dec. 1-4, 1992; UA096.002.010.00072 (Box 10)
  - Dec. 7-11, 1992; UA096.002.010.00073 (Box 10)
  - Dec. 14, 1992; UA096.002.010.00074 (Box 10)
  - Jan. 28, 1993; UA096.002.010.00075 (Box 10)
  - Jan. 29, 1993; UA096.002.010.00076 (Box 10)
  - Feb. 26, 1993; UA096.002.010.00077 (Box 10)
  - March 4, 1993; UA096.002.010.00078 (Box 10)
  - March 5, 1993; UA096.002.010.00079 (Box 10)
  - April 14, 1993; UA096.002.010.00080 (Box 10)
  - April 15, 1993; UA096.002.010.00081 (Box 10)
  - May 19, 1993; UA096.002.010.00082 (Box 10)
  - May 20, 1993; UA096.002.010.00083 (Box 10)
  - June 30, 1993; UA096.002.010.00084 (Box 10)
  - July 1, 1993; UA096.002.010.00085 (Box 10)
  - August 11, 1993; UA096.002.010.00086 (Box 10)
  - August 12, 1993; UA096.002.010.00087 (Box 10)
  - Sept. 22, 1993; UA096.002.010.00088 (Box 10)
  - Sept. 23, 1993; UA096.002.010.00089 (Box 10)
  - P & P - Annual reciew, Nov 3, 1993: registration, UA096.002.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - P & P annual review, Nov. 3, 1993 - Agenda, UA096.002.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - P & P - annual review, Nov 3, 1993: course faculty, UA096.002.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - P & P - annual review, Nov 3, 1993: daily attendance, exam sign-out, UA096.002.011.00004 (Box 11)
  - P & P annual review, Nov 3, 1993: examination results, UA096.002.011.00005 (Box 11)
  - P & P annual review, Nov 3, 1993: grade letters, UA096.002.011.00006 (Box 11)
  - P & P annual reView, Nov 3, 1993: evaluations, UA096.002.011.00007 (Box 11)
  - P & P-annual review, Nov 3, 1993: dept. of labor, UA096.002.011.00008 (Box 11)
  - INSP/MGT-annual rev. Nov 4, 1993 - registraton, UA096.002.011.00009 (Box 11)
  - P & P - annual review, Dec. 15, 1993: agenda, UA096.002.011.00010 (Box 11)
  - P & P - annual review, Dec. 15, 1993: daily attendance / exam sign-out, UA096.002.011.00011 (Box 11)
  - P & P-annual review, Dec. 15, 1993: examination results, UA096.002.011.00012 (Box 11)
  - P& P - annual review, Dec. 15, 1993: grade letters, UA096.002.011.00013 (Box 11)
  - P & P - annual review, Dec 15, 1993: dept. of labor, UA096.002.011.00014 (Box 11)
  - P & P - annual review - Dec 15, 1993 - registrations, UA096.002.011.00015 (Box 11)
  - INSP/MGT - annual rev. Dec 16, 1993: agenda, UA096.002.011.00016 (Box 11)
  - INSP/MGT annual rev. Dec 16, 1993:daily attendance, exam sign-out, UA096.002.011.00017 (Box 11)
  - INSP/MGT - annual rev. Dec 16, 1993: examination results, UA096.002.011.00018 (Box 11)
  - INSP/MGT - annual rev. Dec 16, 1993: grade letters, UA096.002.011.00019 (Box 11)
  - INSP/MGT - annual rev. Dec 16, 1993: registration, UA096.002.011.00020 (Box 11)
  - INSP/MGT - annual rec. Dec 16, 1993: dept. of labor, UA096.002.011.00021 (Box 11)
  - INSP/MGT - annual rec. Dec 16, 1993: grade letters, UA096.002.011.00022 (Box 11)
  - Jan 27, 1994 p & p pse: daily attendnace, sign-out, UA096.002.011.00023 (Box 11)
  - Jan 27, 1994 p & p pse: registration, UA096.002.011.00024 (Box 11)
  - Jan 27, 1994 p & p pse: examination results, UA096.002.011.00025 (Box 11)
  - Jan 27, 1994 p & p pse: dept. of labor, UA096.002.011.00026 (Box 11)
  - March 3, 1994, P&P P5F, Jan 28, 1994 IIMP M3B: Registration, UA096.002.011.00027 (Box 11)
  - March 4, 1994, I/MP M3C: Agenda, UA096.002.011.00028 (Box 11)
  - April 14,1994 P & P P5G: April 14,1994 P & P P5G, UA096.002.011.00030 (Box 11)
  - April 14,1994 P & P P5G: Agenda, UA096.002.011.00031 (Box 11)
  - April 14,1994 P & P P5G: Registration, UA096.002.011.00032 (Box 11)
  - April 14,1994 P & P P5G: Daily attendance / sign-out, UA096.002.011.00033 (Box 11)
  - April 14,1994 P & P P5G: Grade letters, UA096.002.011.00034 (Box 11)
  - April 14,1994 P & P P5G: Dept. of Labor, UA096.002.011.00035 (Box 11)
  - April 15,1994 I/MP M3D: April 15,1994 IIMP M3D, UA096.002.011.00036 (Box 11)
  - April 15,1994 I/MP M3D: Agenda, UA096.002.011.00037 (Box 11)
  - April 15,1994 I/MP M3D: Registration, UA096.002.011.00038 (Box 11)
  - April 15,1994 I/MP M3D: Daily attendance / sign-out, UA096.002.011.00039 (Box 11)
  - April 15,1994 I/MP M3D: Examination results, UA096.002.011.00040 (Box 11)
  - April 15,1994 I/MP M3D: Grade letters, UA096.002.011.00041 (Box 11)
  - April 15,1994 I/MP M3D: Dept. of Labor, UA096.002.011.00042 (Box 11)
  - P & P Annual Review Test, 1994; UA096.002.011.00043 (Box 11)
  - P & P Annual Review, 1994; UA096.002.011.00044 (Box 11)
  - INSP. only Annual Review 15 Questions, A-Ne, 1994; UA096.002.011.00045 (Box 11)
  - IMP Annual Review 30 Questions, A-Ne, 1994; UA096.002.011.00046 (Box 11)
  - [Unknown Date], 1990 -- 1995; UA096.002.011.00047 (Box 11)
  - [Circa 90-91 (copyright incorrect)], 1990 -- 1991; UA096.002.011.00048 (Box 11)
  - [Workshop binder 1 of 2], 1989; UA096.002.011.00049 (Box 11)
  - [Workshop binder 2 of 2], 1989; UA096.002.011.00050 (Box 11)
  - [Workshop binder 1 of 2], 1990; UA096.002.011.00051 (Box 11)
  - [Workshop binder 2 of 2], 1990; UA096.002.011.00052 (Box 11)
  - [Industrial Environmental Management Practices, July 17, 1990], 1907 -- 1990; UA096.002.011.00053 (Box 11)
  - [Workshop Dillon - Forum 6/5/90], 1906 -- 1990; UA096.002.011.00054 (Box 11)
  - [Forest Pest Management Computer Simulation Workshop, Dec. 6, 1991], 1912 -- 1991; UA096.002.011.00055 (Box 11)
  - [Leadership workshop binder 1 of 2], 1991; UA096.002.011.00056 (Box 11)
  - [Leadership workshop binder 2 of 2], 1991; UA096.002.011.00057 (Box 11)
- Project Applications, Reviews, and Reports, 1986 -- 1996; UA096.003; 6.0 Linear Feet
  The series contains projects funded by the Environmental Protection Agency and administered by CEM. The series contains lists of projects for specific fiscal years and project proposals (approved and rejected), committee reviews of proposals, and final reports of projects. General material regarding project application and guidelines for final projects are filed at the beginning of the series. The "Current Projects" booklets can be found prior to the related fiscal year. Many of the final reports include floppy disks.
  This series is divided into proposals (approved, not approved) and final reports. Proposals are arranged chronologically by fiscal year and then last name of applicant. Final reports of projects are arranged by last name of researcher.
  - Projects, 1986 -- 1994; UA096.003.001
    - Program announcements and request for proposal, 1986 -- 1992; UA096.003.012.00001 (Box 12)
      The year is the Fiscal Year.
    - Summary of projects, 1986 -- 1993; UA096.003.012.00002 (Box 12)
    - Shanabruch, W. Proposal, 1987; UA096.003.012.00003 (Box 12)
    - Rowan, A. Correspondence, 1988; UA096.003.012.00004 (Box 12)
    - Rowan, A. Proposal, 1988; UA096.003.012.00005 (Box 12)
    - Shanabruch, W. correspondence, 1988; UA096.003.012.00006 (Box 12)
    - Walt, D. correspondence, 1988; UA096.003.012.00007 (Box 12)
    - Walt, David R., 1988; UA096.003.012.00008 (Box 12)
    - Final research reports publication guidelines, 1989; UA096.003.012.00009 (Box 12)
    - Rappaport, Ann. Project approval form, 1989; UA096.003.012.00010 (Box 12)
    - Soto, A. correspondence, 1989; UA096.003.012.00011 (Box 12)
    - Soto, A. proposal, 1989; UA096.003.012.00012 (Box 12)
    - Verma, S. correspondence, 1989; UA096.003.012.00013 (Box 12)
    - Abstracts, 1990; UA096.003.012.00014 (Box 12)
    - Current projects, 1990; UA096.003.012.00015 (Box 12)
    - Cortese, 1990; UA096.003.012.00016 (Box 12)
    - Robbat amendment, $17,231, 1990; UA096.003.012.00017 (Box 12)
    - Robbat amendment, 1990; UA096.003.012.00018 (Box 12)
    - Stoukids, M. Proposal, 1990; UA096.003.012.00019 (Box 12)
    - White (Rappaport), 1990; UA096.003.012.00020 (Box 12)
    - Brown, L., U.S. and Japan, 1990; UA096.003.012.00021 (Box 12)
    - Current Projects, 1991; UA096.003.012.00022 (Box 12)
    - Chew, Francis, 1991; UA096.003.012.00023 (Box 12)
    - Cole, Brenda and Anne Chabot., 1991; UA096.003.012.00024 (Box 12)
    - Dillon, Patricia S. and Michael S. Baram, 1991; UA096.003.012.00025 (Box 12)
    - Flaherty, Margaret, 1991; UA096.003.012.00026 (Box 12)
    - Green, Sharon N., 1991; UA096.003.012.00027 (Box 12)
    - Hecht, Norman B., 1991; UA096.003.012.00028 (Box 12)
    - Hollister, Robert M., 1991; UA096.003.012.00029 (Box 12)
    - Hyde, James N. and David Gute, 1991; UA096.003.012.00030 (Box 12)
    - Kenny, Jonathon E., 1991; UA096.003.012.00031 (Box 12)
    - Kounaves, Samuel, 1991; UA096.003.012.00032 (Box 12)
    - Krimsky, Sheldon, 1991; UA096.003.012.00033 (Box 12)
    - Leav, Irwin and Shuk Mei Ho, 1991; UA096.003.012.00034 (Box 12)
    - Leavy, Stuat and Richard Wetzler, 1991; UA096.003.012.00035 (Box 12)